https://oarc.duke.edu/privacy/duke-university-privacy-statement

Skip to main content
You are hereHomePrivacyDuke University Privacy Statement
Duke Alert Bar
Duke University Privacy Statement
Duke University is committed to fairly and appropriately managing and safeguarding the information collected, used and maintained in support of its missions and to transparency regarding our data management practices. Duke respects the integrity of all its stakeholders, including as represented by personally identifying information about each stakeholder, and takes seriously its responsibility to protect individuals’ privacy in balance with meeting its legal, policy and administrative obligations.
The following describes how information is collected, used and maintained at Duke, including how websites in the Duke.edu domain collect, use and share information about those who engage with Duke University sites. This privacy statement covers all Duke.edu websites unless a particular website indicates otherwise.
For information specific to jurisdictions with additional notice requirements, including the European Economic Area (EEA), please click here for the full policy and the data subject request form. In addition, and for ease of reference, please see the following for Duke’s privacy practices in specific areas at the University.
Admissions/Financial Aid
Duke University Press Customers
Research
Alumni
Human Resources
Students
Donors
Online/Non-credit Education
Website
Our Information Collection and Use Practices
Duke University may use information you provide, in all formats, to meet our obligations to you as a stakeholder, to respond to your inquiries and for our own marketing and development purposes. Duke may use information you submit through our websites for these purposes as well.
Duke.edu websites may collect personally identifiable information about you when you visit the site to facilitate providing you with online services. This information may include your name and contact information (email, address, telephone number) and other identifiers as necessary for the online application or service, to register for events, to enhance our offerings and web services, and to provide website feedback.
Duke may reveal personally identifiable information about you to unaffiliated third parties:
if you authorize or request it to facilitate a transaction on your behalf;
if Duke must comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or other stakeholders (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection, etc.);
if the information is provided to our vendors, service providers or agents to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, processing orders, etc.);
if the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets); or
as otherwise described in this Privacy Statement and any documentation to which it is linked.
We may share information that does not personally identify you without restriction.
Cookies and Website Analytics
Duke websites employ cookies and similar technology to collect aggregate (non-personal) information about your website usage. This allows Duke websites to remember you when you login in the future and to know your preferences when you return to Duke websites. Cookies may remain on your browser, unless you delete them or they expire. Please be advised that some cookies may remain for a period of time while others are erased when you close your browser window. You may adjust your browser settings and decline cookies, but this may impact some features of some Duke websites. To learn more information about cookies and how they work, visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
Many Duke.edu websites use Google Analytics (or other similar web analytics tools) to collect information about visitor traffic and their behavior on our sites. We use these tools to identify usage trends, to improve the performance and to enhance the content of our websites. When we use these tools, we do not use them to identify you and we limit the collection or storage of your personal information.
To Unsubscribe
Should you wish to unsubscribe from receiving emails from a particular Duke department or a Duke.edu domain, you may do so by unsubscribing through the unsubscribe feature included in specific emails, or by requesting this at privacy@duke.edu. Please note that Duke will not unsubscribe you from emails about your account or your transactions with us.
Updates to this Privacy Statement
Duke University reserves the right to modify all statements made about its privacy practices. We encourage you to return to this page frequently to check for updated information and effective dates.
Your continued engagement with Duke after any changes to this Privacy Statement go into effect, in person or through our websites, constitutes your acceptance of the changes.
Contact Information
If you have questions about this Privacy Statement or any privacy practices at Duke University, please contact privacy@duke.edu.
Sponsored Programs Assurance and Research Compliance (SPARC)
Duke Health Integrity Line and Duke Speak Up Program: (800) 826-8109
Animal Welfare Hotline: (919) 684-3535
